Finding Aid for the Recordings of Evenings for New Music, 1964-1980
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Service copy compact discs reformatted from reel to reel tapes, 1964-1980, I.; CD 1-139
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 52, May 3, 1969, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 65-Reel 66 Preservation copy on DVD 31 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 43-44)
    Goodbye music (1969)
    Performers: Jon Hassell, amplified zither; Terry Riley, organ
    Duration: 23:14
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 54, November 8, 1969, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 67-Reel 68 Preservation copy on DVD 32 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 45-46)
    Work number: ENM054-01
    Blauvelt, Ralph
    Prelude and invention for player piano and piano player (1969)
    Performers: Ronald Peters, piano; assisted by Ralph Blauvelt
    Duration: 5:44
    Work number: ENM054-02
    Westergaard, Peter
    Variations for six players (1963)
    Performers: Thomas Howell, flute; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; William Furioso, percussion; Ronald Peters, piano; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 10:41
    Work number: ENM054-03
    Paradigm For my friends (New version 1968-69)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Steven Bell, guitar; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Jan Williams, percussion/conductor
    Duration: 20:04
    Work number: ENM054-04
    Burnham, Edward
    Trans-dance (1969)
    Performers: Edward Burnham, percussion and tape
    Duration: 10:32
    Work number: ENM054-05
    Fulkerson, James
    For Norma (1968)
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Thomas Howell, flute; James Fulkerson, trombone; Gerald Cash, percussion; Julius Eastman, piano; Marijke Verberne, violoncello
    Duration: 10:01
    Work number: ENM054-06
    Gaburo, Kenneth
    Antiphony IV (1966-67)
    Performers: Thomas Howell, flute; James Fulkerson, trombone; James Kurzdorfer, bass; Peter Gena, tape
    Duration: 9:26
    Work number: ENM054-07
    Childs, Barney
    Jack's new bag (1967)
    Performers: Thomas Howell, flute; Frank Collura, trumpet; James Fulkerson, trombone; Gerald Cash, Edward Burnham, percussion; Julius Eastman, Ronald Peters, pianos; Sheila Braunstein, viola; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; James Kurzdorfer, bass; Lejaren Hiller, conductor
    Duration: 8:38
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 56, December 13, 1969, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 69-Reel 71 Preservation copy on DVD 33 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 47-48)
    Work number: ENM056-01
    Jones, David
    Exits and enterances (1969)
    Performers: Thomas Howell, Petr Kotík, flutes; Jerry Kirkbride, Roberto Laneri, clarinets; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; James Fulkerson, trombone; Gerald Cash, percussion; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Lejaren Hiller, conductor
    Duration: 12:37
    Work number: ENM056-02
    Purswell, Patrick
    It grew and grew (1965)
    Performers: Thomas Howell, flute
    Duration: 6:23
    Work number: ENM056-03
    Scherzo for piano (1958)
    Performers: Ronald Peters, piano
    Duration: 12:45
    Work number: ENM056-04
    Nordheim, Arne
    Colorazione (1968)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, organ; Edward Burnham, percussion; Arne Nordheim, Petr Kotík, George Ritscher, electronicists
    Duration: 20:34
    Work number: ENM056-05
    Anhalt, István
    Foci (1969)
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Thomas Howell, flute; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Ralph Blauvelt, trumpet; James Fulkerson, trombone; Gerald Cash, William Furioso, percussion; Julius Eastman, Stephen Manes, pianos; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Tom Coleman, bass; Judith Sherman, Peter Gena, Roberto Laneri, tape recorders; István Anhalt, conductor
    Duration: 32:42
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 59, February 8, 1970, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 72-Reel 73 Preservation copy on DVD 34 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 49)
    Work number: ENM059-01
    Adieu (1966)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; William Lane, horn
    Work number: ENM059-02
    Algorithms I, version I (1968)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Frank Collura, trumpet; Edward Burnham, percussion; Mario Falcao, harp; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; James Kurzdorfer, bass; George Ritscher, tape recorder; Lejaren Hiller, conductor
    Duration: 10:23
    Work number: ENM059-03
    Algorithms I, version IV (1968)
    Duration: 10:07
    Work number: ENM059-04
    Chadabe, Joel
    Monomusic (1969)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; John Heitman, alto flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Frank Collura, trumpet; Mario Falcao, harp; Charles Haupt, violin; Diane Williams, viola; Joel Chadabe, conductor
    Duration: 8:22
    Work number: ENM059-05
    Brün, Herbert, 1918-2000
    Non sequitur VI (1966)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; William Furioso, Jan Williams, percussion; Stephen Manes, piano; Mario Falcao, harp; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Herbert Brün, conductor
    Duration: 12:57
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 64, March 22, 1970, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 74-Reel 76 Preservation copy on DVD 35 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 50)
    Work number: ENM064-01
    Pinto, Carlo, 1925-
    Interference '69 (1969)
    Performers: Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Gerald Cash, percussion; Stephen Manes, piano; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Carlo Pinto, conductor
    Duration: 9:03
    Work number: ENM064-02
    Schwartz, Elliott, 1936-
    Signals (1968)
    Performers: James Fulkerson, trombone; Nicholas Molfese, bass
    Duration: 7:43
    Work number: ENM064-03
    Fantasy for violin and piano, op. 47 (1949)
    Performers: Charles Haupt, violin; Stephen Manes, piano
    Duration: 8:56
    Work number: ENM064-04
    Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946
    Concerto for harpsichord, flute, oboe, clarinet, violin and cello (1923-26)
    Performers: John Heitman, flute; Eugene Steinberg, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Ronald Peters, harpsichord; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Donald Shrimpton, conductor
    Work number: ENM064-05
    Kotík Petr
    Kontrapunkt 2 (1962-63)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Eugene Steinberg, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Diane Williams, viola; Marijke Verberne, violoncello
    Duration: 11:20
    Work number: ENM064-06
    Rychlik, Jan, 1916-1964
    African cycle (1962)
    Performers: John Heitman, flute; Eugene Steinberg, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; William Lane, Kenneth Wells, horns; James Fulkerson, Michael Keller, trombones; Stephen Manes, piano; Petr Kotík, conductor
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 66, May 3, 1970, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 77 Preservation copy on DVD 36 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 51-52)
    Work number: ENM066-01
    Yun, Isang
    Loyang (1962)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Jerry Kirkbride, clarinet; Darlene Reynard, bassoon; Mario Falcao, harp; Gerald Cash, William Furioso, percussion; Charles Haupt, violin; Marijke Verberne, violoncello; Jacques Guyonnet, conductor
    Duration: 16:55
    Work number: ENM066-02
    Wyttenbach, Jürg
    Three pieces for piano (1969)
    Performers: Evelyne Crochet, piano
    Work number: ENM066-03
    Becker, John J.
    At Dieppe (1959)
    Performers: Gwendolin Sims, soprano; Evelyne Crochet, piano
    Duration: 7:01
    Work number: ENM066-04
    Guyonnet, Jacques, 1933-
    Good grief, Jerry (1970)
    Performers: Ensemble; Jacques Guyonnet, conductor
    Duration: 35:15
    Work number: ENM066-05
    Thruway (1970)
    Performers: East High School A Cappella Choir, Buffalo, New York, Donald Hilliard, director; ensemble; Julius Eastman, conductor
    Duration: 31:30
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 68, November 1, 1970, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 78-Reel 79 Preservation copy on DVD 37 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 53-54)
    Work number: ENM068-01
    Orgad, Ben-Zion, 1926-2006
    Trio for strings (1961)
    Performers: Mark Sokol, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; Douglas Davis, violoncello
    Duration: 14:14
    Work number: ENM068-02
    Cocktail music for piano (1962)
    Performers: Roger Shields, piano
    Duration: 4:31
    Work number: ENM068-03
    Lanza, Alcides
    Penetrations V (1970)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Robert Laneri, clarinet; James Fulkerson, trombone, Howard Zwickler, William Furioso, percussion; Jesse Levine, viola; George Ritscher, Stuart Fox, electronics, Edward Cox, Geoffrey Germony, lighting; Jan Williams, conductor lighting; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 13:41
    Work number: ENM068-04
    Davies, Peter Maxwell, 1934-
    Eight songs for a mad king (1969)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, voice; Petr Kotík, flute; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Howard Zwickler, percussion; Roger Shields, piano; Mark Sokol, violin; Douglas Davis, violoncello; Lukas Foss, conductor
    Duration: 27:12
    Work number: ENM068-04a
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 69, December 6, 1970, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 80-Reel 81 Preservation copy on DVD 38 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 55)
    Work number: ENM069-01
    Amores (1943)
    Performers: Roger Shields, prepared piano; Thomas Rienzi, Jan Williams, William Furioso, percussion
    Duration: 10:54
    Work number: ENM069-02
    Druckman, Jacob, 1928-1996
    Animus I (1966)
    Performers: James Fulkerson, trombone
    Duration: 12:44
    Work number: ENM069-03
    All set (1957)
    Performers: Edward Yadzinski, Jeff Silberman, saxophones; Dave Kuen, trumpet; James Fulkerson, trombone; William Furioso, Howard Zwickler, percussion; Roger Shields, piano; Nicholas Molfese, bass; Lejaren Hiller, conductor
    Work number: ENM069-04
    Sonata, violin-piano, no. 4 (1905-24)
    Performers: Mark Sokol, violin; Roger Shields, piano
    Duration: 9:36
    Work number: ENM069-05
    Hellermann, William
    Formata (1967)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; James Fulkerson, trombone; Howard Zwickler, percussion; Stephen Manes, piano; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 7:40
    Work number: ENM069-06
    Williams, Jan
    Dream lesson (1970)
    Performers: Jan Williams, piano; Edward Yadzinski, lighting
    Duration: 10:02
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 71, February 14, 1971, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 82 Preservation copy on DVD 39 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 56)
    Work number: ENM071-01
    Schat, Peter, 1935-
    Improvisations uit het labyrint (1964)
    Performers: Judith Sherman, Julius Eastman, John Thomas, voices; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; William Furioso, percussion; James Whitman, piano; Fred Stroud, bass
    Duration: 8:57
    Work number: ENM071-02
    Yuasa, Joji
    Projection for violoncello and piano (1967)
    Performers: Douglas Davis, violoncello; Roger Shields, piano
    Duration: 6:22
    Work number: ENM071-03
    Takemitsu, Toru
    Sacrifice (1962)
    Performers: John Heitmann, alto flute; William Furioso, percussion; Stuart Fox, guitar
    Work number: ENM071-04
    Miroglio, Francis
    Refractions (1968)
    Performers: Peter Kotík, flute; Jan Williams, percussion; Roger Shields, piano
    Duration: 9:59
    Work number: ENM071-05
    Harrison, Lou, 1917-2003
    Concerto for the violin (1959)
    Performers: Mark Sokol, violin; U. B. Percussion Ensemble; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 20:53
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 71(a): Copy, February 14, 1971, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 83 Preservation copy on DVD 40 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 57)
    Work number: ENM071-01a
    Work number: ENM071-02a
    Work number: ENM071-03a
    Work number: ENM071-04a
    Work number: ENM071-05a
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 75, March 25, 1971, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 84 Preservation copy on DVD 41 Performed at Domus Theater (Box 2, Cd 58)
    Work number: ENM075-01
    Alley, Book no. 1 (1970)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, piano; Mark Sokol, Rhoda Gena, violins; Diane Williams, viola; Douglas Davis, violoncello; Petr Kotík, flute, conductor; Ellis Wean, tuba; James Fulkerson, trombone; Jan Williams, piano; Donald Montalto, Kenneth Hafner, Andrew Ploch, trumpet; Jeff Silberman, tenor saxophone; Ronald Richards, oboe; Roberto Lanieri, bass clarinet
    Duration: 31:15
    Work number: ENM075-02
    Trumpet (1970)
    Performers: Frank Collura, Donald Montalto, Kenneth Hafner, Andrew Ploch, trumpet; Jeff Silberman, tenor saxophone; Roberto Lanieri, clarinet; Ronald Richards, oboe; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 21:40
    Work number: ENM075-03
    Komorous, Rudolf
    Lady Blancarosa: an opera in one act (1967)
    Performers: Adrienne Tworek as Helga; Julius Eastman as Kamilla; Terry Moore as Dwarf Erik, George Ritscher, tape operator
    Duration: 15:00
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 77, May 1, 1971, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 85, Reel 87 Preservation copy on DVD 42 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery Includes introductory remarks. (Box 2, Cd 59-60)
    Work number: ENM077-01
    Kondo, Jo, 1947-
    Breeze for 9 players (1970)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, John Heitman, flutes; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; James Fulkerson, trombone; Howard Zwickler, Paul Mouradian, percussion; Stuart Fox, guitar; James Kurzdorfer, bass
    Duration: 15:55
    Work number: ENM077-02
    Rosenberg, Wolf, 1915-1996
    Crockett (1970-71)
    Performers: Laurence Bogue, baritone; Petr Kotík, flute; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; James Fulkerson, trombone; Stuart Fox, guitar; Mark Sokol, violin; James Kurzdorfer, bass, James Hurt, actor
    Duration: 22:25
    Work number: ENM077-03
    Sonata, violin, piano, no. 3 (1970)
    Duration: 16:00
    Work number: ENM077-04
    Three rituals for two percussionists and lights (1970)
    Performers: Jan Williams, Howard Zwickler, percussion; Roberta Friedham, Grahame Weinbren, lighting
    Duration: 42:01
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 77(a): Partial copy, May 1, 1971, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 86 Preservation copy on DVD 43 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery Includes spoken remarks. (Box 2, Cd 61)
    Work number: ENM077a-01a
    Work number: ENM077a-02a
    Work number: ENM077a-03a
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 78, October 30, 1971, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 88-Reel 89 Preservation copy on DVD 44 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 62-63)
    Work number: ENM078-01
    Brant, Henry, 1913-
    Ice age (1954)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Garry Kvistad, percussion; Roger Shields, piano
    Duration: 7:14
    Work number: ENM078-02
    Tremblay, Gilles
    "... le sifflement des vents-porteurs de l'amour..." (1970)
    Performers: Robert Cram, flute; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 12:27
    Work number: ENM078-03
    Match (1964)
    Performers: Garry Kvistad, percussion; Douglas Davis, Tsuyoshi Tsitsumi, violoncellos
    Duration: 17:15
    Work number: ENM078-04
    Stiller, Andrew
    Ctenophores (1967)
    Performers: Garry Kvistad, Jeffrey Kowalsky, Larry Stein, Andrew Ziemba, percussion; Michael Collier, harpsichord; Mario Falcao, harp; Stuart Fox, guitar; Clifford Stoll, tape; Roberto Laneri, slides
    Duration: 27:49
    Work number: ENM078-05
    Machine music (1964)
    Performers: Jeffrey Kowalsky, percussion; Roger Shields, piano; Stuart Fox, tape
    Duration: 12:59
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 78(a): partial copy, October 30, 1971, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 90 Preservation copy on DVD 45 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 64)
    Work number: ENM078a-02a
    Work number: ENM078a-03a
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 83, December 12, 1971, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 91-Reel 92 Preservation copy on DVD 46 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 65-66)
    Work number: ENM083-01
    Shinohara, Makoto
    Consonance (1964-67)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Beye Fyfe, horn; Jeffery Kowalsky, vibes; Garry Kvistad, marimba; Mario Falcao, harp; Douglas Davis, violoncello; Julius Eastman, conductor
    Duration: 10:15
    Work number: ENM083-02
    Beglarian, Grant
    Of fables, foibles and fancies (1971)
    Performers: Terry Moore, reciter/actor; Douglas Davis, violoncello
    Duration: 14:50
    Work number: ENM083-03
    Les moutons des Panurge (1969)
    Performers: Frederic Rzewski and ensemble
    Duration: 15:58
    Work number: ENM083-04
    Sonata, violoncello-piano (1914) and Three little pieces, op. 11 (1914)
    Duration: 4:27
    Work number: ENM083-05
    Sonatine (1946)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Frederic Rzewski, piano
    Duration: 14:36
    Work number: ENM083-06
    Erickson, Robert, 1917-1997
    Concerto for piano and seven instruments (1963)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; Donald Montalto, trumpet; James Fulkerson, trombone; Garry Kvistad, percussion; Roger Shields, piano; Dennis Allen, bass; Jan Williams, conductor
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 84, February 13, 1972, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 93 Preservation copy on DVD 47 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 67-68)
    Work number: ENM084-01
    Solitaire (1971)
    Performers: Richard Trythall, piano
    Duration: 13:37
    Work number: ENM084-02
    Channel firing (1970)
    Performers: Laurence Bogue, baritone; Richard Trythall, piano
    Duration: 3:53
    Work number: ENM084-03
    Myopia A night (1971)
    Performers: Laurence Bogue, baritone; Petr Kotík, flute; Donald Montalto, trumpet; Lee Lovallo, trombone; Henry Rubin, violin; Douglas Davis, violoncello; Leo Smit, conductor
    Duration: 5:18
    Work number: ENM084-04
    Ni bruit ni vitesse (1971)
    Performers: Lukas Foss, piano; Jan Williams, percussion
    Duration: 13:58
    Work number: ENM084-05
    Macle (1971)
    Performers: John R. Adams, Petr Kotík, Roberto Laneri, Jan Williams, amplified voices; Julius Eastman, electronics
    Duration: 32:58
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 88, March 19, 1972, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 94 Preservation copy on DVD 48 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 69)
    Work number: ENM088-01
    Anaktoria (1969)
    Performers: Edward Yadzinski, clarinet; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; William Lane, horn; Henry Rubin, Jacquelynne Leonard, violins; Jesse Levine, viola; Douglas Davis, violoncello; Louis Bruno, bass; Lukas Foss, conductor
    Duration: 12:06
    Work number: ENM088-02
    Matthews, Justus Frederick
    Four miniatures (1967-68)
    Performers: Stuart Fox, guitar; Douglas Davis, violoncello; Louis Bruno, bass
    Duration: 2:12
    Work number: ENM088-03
    Perle, George, 1915-
    Sonata quasi una fantasia (1972)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; George Perle, piano
    Duration: 10:03
    Work number: ENM088-04
    Salvos (1964)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion; Henry Rubin, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; Mary Lane, violoncello; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 6:16
    Work number: ENM088-05
    Kontakte, Nr. 12 (1959-60)
    Performers: Garry Kvistad, percussion; Richard Trythall, piano; tape
    Duration: 34:45
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 91, April 30, 1972, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 95-Reel 96 Preservation copy on DVD 49 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 70-71)
    Work number: ENM091-01
    Concertino de printemps (1934)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; William Lane, horn; Dave Kuehn, trumpet; Garry Kvistad, percussion; Henry Rubin, violin solo; Marie Yadzinski, Jon Shallit, violins; Jesse Levine, viola; Wendel Haver, violoncello; Louis Bruno, bass; Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 9:06
    Work number: ENM091-02
    Symphony (1972)
    Performers: Petr Kotík, flute; Garry Kvistad, Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion; Richard Trythall, piano; Michael Sahl, organ; Stuart Fox, guitar; Henry Rubin, violin, Jan Williams, conductor
    Duration: 20:56
    Work number: ENM091-03
    Correspondences (1969)
    Performers: Roberto Laneri, clarinet; Vinko Globokar, trombone; Jan Williams, percussion; Stuart Fox, guitar
    Duration: 15:38
    Work number: ENM091-04
    Discours II (1970)
    Performers: Vinko Globokar, trombone; tape
    Duration: 13:55
    Work number: ENM091-05
    Schafer, R. Murray
    Requiem for the party-girl (1966)
    Performers: Julius Eastman, voice; Petr Kotík, flute; Roberto Laneri, clarinet; William Lane, horn; Garry Kvistad, percussion; Richard Trythall, piano; Mario Falcao, harp; Henry Rubin, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; Wendell Haver, violoncello
    Duration: 15:30
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 91(a): Partial copy, April 30, 1972, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 97 Preservation copy on DVD 50 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 72)
    Work number: ENM091a-02a
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 93, October 28, 1972, 2 compact discs; Transferred from: Reel 98 Preservation copy on DVD 51 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 73)
    Work number: ENM093-01
    Vintage Alice (1972)
    Performers: Sylvia Dimiziani, soprano/narrator; Petr Kotík, flute; Ronald Richards, oboe; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Andrew Stiller, bassoon; Edward Yadzinski, Phil DiRe, saxophones; William Lane, Beye Fyfe, horns; Dave Kuehn, trumpet; Donald Miller, trombone; Dennis Kahle, Jeffery Kowalsky, percussion; Oswald Rantucci, mandolin; Andrew Frech, banjo; Guy Klucevsek, accordion; Henry Rubin, Jacqueline Leonard, violins; Len Matczynski, viola; David Gibson, violoncello; Edwin Gordon, bass; David Del Tredici, conductor
    Duration: 27:53
    Work number: ENM093-02
    Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987
    Pianos and voices (1972)
    Performers: William Appleby, David Del Tredici, Julius Eastman, Morton Feldman, Lukas Foss, pianos
    Duration: 42:57
  - Evenings for New Music Concert 94, December 3, 1972, 1 compact disc; Transferred from: Reel 99-Reel 100 Preservation copy on DVD 52 Performed at Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2, Cd 74-75)
    Work number: ENM094-01
    Helps, Robert
    Serenade (1960-64)
    Performers: William Lane, horn; David Del. Tredici, piano; Henry Rubin, Marie Yadzinski, violins; Frank Reilly, viola; David Gibson, violoncello
    Work number: ENM094-02
    Wyner, Yehudi, 1929-
    De Novo (1971)
    Performers: Petr Kotik, flute; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Henry Rubin, violin; Frank Reilly, viola; David Gibson, violoncello; Louis Bruno, bass
    Work number: ENM094-03
    Three airs for Frank O'Hara's angel (1972)
    Performers: Sylvia Dimiziani, soprano; Fredonia Chamber Singers, SUC at Fredonia, William Graf, director; Dennis Kahle, percussion; Lukas Foss, piano; Oswald Rantucci, mandolin; Guy Klucevsek, accordion; tape
    Duration: 9:14
    Work number: ENM094-04
    Seasons (1970)
    Performers: Lynn Harbold, Dennis Kahle, Jeffery Kowalsky, Jan Williams, percussion; tape
    Duration: 16:17
    Work number: ENM094-05
    Night conjure-verse (1965)
    Performers: Sylvia Dimiziani, soprano; Julius Eastman, countertenor; Eiko Ito, Petr Kotik, flutes; Eugene Steinberg, oboe; Amrom Chodos, clarinet; Edward Yadzinski, bass clarinet; Nelson Dayton, bassoon; William Lane, horn; Henry Rubin, Marie Yadzinski, violins; Fra
    Duration: 17:52